Records of the Women’s Center of the Southern Tier
Elmira College
Records of the Women’s Center of the Southern Tier
1985 - 2002
The collection consists of board minutes and newsletters from 1985-2002.
1 Linear ft. (1 box)
Women’s Center of the Southern Tier
Elmira College Archives, Gannett-Tripp Library, Elmira College, Elmira, N.Y.
Unrestricted
The Women’s Center of the Southern Tier was incorporated in 1985 as a non-profit organization dedicated to providing information and assistance to women of all ages and circumstances who live in the Southern Tier.
Women’s Center of the Southern Tier; minutes (units for duration); newsletters
The records consist exclusively of board minutes and meeting materials with an incomplete run of newsletters dating from 1985 - 2002.
ORGANIZATIONAL NOTE: The collection is organized chronologically with board related materials first and newsletters at the end.
- Board Meetings - [1985-1990] (Box-folder 1 1)
- Board Meetings - [1993-1994] (Box-folder 1 2)
- Board Meetings - [1994-1995] (Box-folder 1 3)
- Board Meetings - [1995-1996] (Box-folder 1 4)
- Board Meetings - [1996-1997] (Box-folder 1 5)
- Board Meetings - [1997-1998] (Box-folder 1 6)
- Board Meetings - [1998-1999] (Box-folder 1 7)
- Strategic Plan - [1998-1999] (Box-folder 1 8)
- Board Minutes - [1999-2001] (Box-folder 1 9)
- Board Meetings [1999-2002] (Box-folder 1 10)
- Board of Director's Manual [2001?] (Box-folder 1 11)
- Newsletter [1985-1990] (Box-folder 1 12)
- Newsletter [1991-1998] (Box-folder 1 13)
- Newsletter [1999-2002] (Box-folder 1 14)